richellusa.com 2012-05-27

# Richell USA Inc. :: Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

At Richell USA Inc. (“Richell”), we care about your personal privacy and therefore have adopted the practices described in this Privacy Policy. You should not access or use our services until you have carefully read this Privacy Policy and fully understand the terms and conditions described in it. In addition, by using the Richellusa.com website, you have agreed to and are bound by the Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy stated here without modification. 

**Our Use of Your Personal Information:**  We collect and use information about you which we reasonably believe will help us administer our business or provide products, services or other opportunities to you. Among other things, we use the information we learn about you to help us personalize and improve the experience you have with us, to respond to your requests and to communicate with you in a timely manner. 

 **Site Use Information:** You can visit Richell's web site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Our web server collects only the domain names, not the email addresses, of visitors. This information is strictly used to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the Site, pages viewed, etc. Richell utilizes this information to measure the use of our Site and to improve the content of our Site. 

**Registration Information You Provide To Us:**   When you register on our site as a Client/Dealer, we collect profile information from you through your registration form that will allow you to access our Client/Dealer Catalog. We require that you provide your first and last name, email address, company name, etc. and set up a User ID and password in order to login. 

If you wish to advertise or obtain support or contact us with questions or comments regarding our products, services, web site issues or corrections, we require you to provide your full name, email address and country/region as may be required on our “Contact Us” page. At your option you may voluntarily provide your company name, mailing address (i.e., street address, city, state, country and zip/postal code) phone number, etc. to contact us by email. 

By providing this personal information to us, you explicitly agree to our collection and usage of such information as described in this Privacy Policy. Usually, we use your personal information  only to respond to your inquiries, process an order, contact you regarding account status or customer service, let you know about products or services which may be of interest to you, or to allow you to access specific account information. 

**Credit Card Information:** To the extent you register to use the Site to shop for products and/or replacement parts, we may ask for credit card information in connection with payment for these products/services pursuant to our Purchasing/Vendor Agreement with you, if one applies. Richell will not disclose credit card information except to its bank or to authorized credit card processors and accounting companies for the purposes of maintaining your account. 

**Purchase Information:** If you decide to purchase a product posted on our Site, we may require information in addition to that provided in the registration form. This information will be used only to complete your purchase transaction and (if you purchase a product/replacement part from us) for warranty or service purposes. 

 **Cookies:** Like many web sites we use "cookies" to enable us to remember your password, to help us identify the portions of our Site that may be the most relevant for your needs, and to help us identify other products or services that may be of interest to you or others. A cookie is a small piece of information that a web site can store on your web browser and then retrieve at a later time. We use cookies to track the portions of our Site you visit. However, we do NOT use cookies to examine your surfing behavior before or after you leave our Site. 

 **Email Communications:** We use your email address to contact you to respond to your inquiries or to provide information on products or services to you. To help us determine whether you have received an email from us, and to help us make emails more useful and interesting, we may receive a confirmation that you have opened an email from us. 

 **Restrictions on Disclosing Information to Third Parties:**  We are not in the business of selling your personal information to others. We do not reveal any personal information about you to unaffiliated third parties, unless: (1) you request or authorize it; (2) the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you; or (3) the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.).

 **Security Procedures to Protect Information:**  We maintain security standards and procedures to help prevent unauthorized access to confidential information about you. Our site uses encryption technology, secure commerce servers and authentication to protect your personal information. As long as the web browser you are using supports VeriSign (SSL), your information will be submitted to us with a high level of security. We update and test our security technology on an ongoing basis. We also have procedures limiting employee access to personal information. 

 **Inapplicability of Privacy Policies of any Linked Sites or Other Parties:**  Richell's Site may contain links to other sites such as affiliates, subsidiaries or other third party distributors and sales representatives. This Privacy Policy only addresses Richell's use and disclosure of your personal information collected on our site. While we try to link only to sites that share our standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties or the content of linked sites, although we do encourage you to read the applicable privacy policies and terms and conditions of such parties or web sites. 

 **Terms of Use, Notices and Changes to Our Privacy Policy** As our business changes from time to time, we reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use at any time. The use of your information is subject to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use in effect at the time of use. The provisions contained herein supersede all previous notices or statements regarding our privacy practices with respect to this Site. We encourage you to check our Site frequently to see the current Privacy Policy and Terms of Use in effect and any changes that may have been made to them.

For questions or comments, you may contact us directly by writing or calling:

 **Richell USA Inc.  **   
2214 Paddock Way Drive, Suite 500  
Grand Prairie, Texas 75050 USA   
Phone 972-641-9795   
Fax 972-641-8495

Copyright© 2012 Richell USA, Inc. All rights reserved.
